<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<questions>
    <question answer="Use the latest stable version">In mainprompt.xml, it mentions using Vite for setup. Is there a specific version of Vite that should be used, or is the latest version acceptable?</question>
    <question answer="NO">In gamerules.xml, the SUCCESSFUL_ATTEMPTS_REQUIRED is set to 5 for "Chord Mode." Is this value fixed, or should I provide a way for users to configure it in the UI?</question>
    <question answer="NO">In MusicData.json, there are specific chords defined. Should I use only these chords, or should I generate additional chords dynamically based on the provided data?</question>
    <question answer="NO">In Piano.jsx, the onClick prop is used for handling key presses. How should I handle multiple simultaneous key presses, if at all?</question>
    <question answer="auto-detect">Regarding MIDI support, should I attempt to auto-detect and connect to MIDI devices, or should I provide a button for the user to manually request MIDI access?</question>
    <question answer="sequentially">In "Chord Mode," do I need to play the chord progression sequentially, or can I play all chords simultaneously?</question>
    <question answer="add a small delay">How should I handle the timing of note playback in "Chord Mode" to ensure that the progression is clear to the user?</question>
    <question answer="Yes">Should I provide visual feedback for the correct chord notes in "Chord Mode," similar to "Guess the Note" mode?</question>
    <question answer="Material, clean design whenever possible">Is there a specific design or style guide that I should follow for the UI, or can I use my discretion in designing the interface?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Are there any performance considerations I should be aware of, especially regarding the number of keys and audio playback?</question>
    <question answer="NO">How should I handle browser refreshes or navigations away from the app while in the middle of a game mode? Should I persist the state or reset it on reload?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I include any analytics or tracking in in app usage, or app usage?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I need to make support for different languages or localization?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Are there any specific error messages or user feedback that should be displayed in certain scenarios?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I include any kind of scoring system or leaderboards?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Is there a specific tone or voice that should be used in any instructional text or messages?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I consider adding sound effects or background music to enhance the user experience?</question>
    <question answer="Not critical">How important is it to optimize the app for performance, especially on lower-end devices?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Are there any specific accessibility features that need to be implemented beyond the basics?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I consider adding any social sharing capabilities, such as allowing users to share their scores on social media?</question>
    <question answer="open ended">Is there a deadline for completing this task, or is it open-ended?</question>
    <question answer="Working on both will ensure that you don't make breaking changes">Should I focus on completing one mode before starting the other, or can I work on both simultaneously?</question>
    <question answer="Whatever works best with Vite">Are there any specific testing frameworks or methodologies that should be used for testing the app?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I include any kind of tutorial or onboarding process for new users?</question>
    <question answer="Assume users aren't familiar with music theory">Is there a specific way that the app should handle users who are not familiar with music theory?</question>
    <question answer="There might be new modes, keep an open architecture allowing modularity">Should I consider adding more game modes in the future, and if so, how should I structure the code to accommodate this?</question>
    <question answer="Prettier is fine">Are there any specific code quality tools or linters that should be used, such as ESLint or Prettier?</question>
    <question answer="Functional testing is enough. It's important to do it when you have something final, to avoid constant refactoring of the tests">Should I write unit tests or integration tests for the components, or is functional testing sufficient?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Is there a specific way that the app should handle different screen sizes or orientations?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I consider adding any kind of animation or transition effects to enhance the user experience?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Is there a specific way that the app should handle users who are using screen readers or other assistive technologies?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I include any kind of about page or credits section in the app?</question>
    <question answer="Handle clicks and taps">Is there a specific way that the app should handle users who are using touchscreens versus mouse and keyboard?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I consider adding any kind of settings or preferences that users can adjust, such as volume or display options?</question>
    <question answer="Chord mode will be disabled">Is there a specific way that the app should handle users who are using browsers that do not support certain features, such as Web MIDI API?</question>
    <question answer="Add console.log messages when errors happen, to help debugging. Make a centralized log method that will check if a DEBUG mode is on (local CONST), so we can disable console logigng at once">Should I include any kind of feedback mechanism for users to report bugs or suggest improvements?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Is there a specific way that the app should handle users who are using different browsers or browser versions?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I consider adding any kind of advertising or monetization to the app?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Is there a specific way that the app should handle users who are using different operating systems, such as Windows, macOS, iOS, or Android?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I consider adding any kind of user authentication or account system to the app?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Is there a specific way that the app should handle users who are using virtual reality or augmented reality devices?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I consider adding any kind of multiplayer functionality to the app?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Is there a specific way that the app should handle users who are using different input methods, such as voice commands or eye tracking?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I consider adding any kind of machine learning or artificial intelligence to the app?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Is there a specific way that the app should handle users who are using different languages or regional settings?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I consider adding any kind of e-commerce functionality to the app, such as selling virtual goods or subscriptions?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Is there a specific way that the app should handle users who are using different time zones or date formats?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I consider adding any kind of integration with external services, such as social networks or music streaming platforms?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Is there a specific way that the app should handle users who are using different types of devices, such as desktops, laptops, tablets, or smartphones?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I consider adding any kind of virtual reality or augmented reality experiences to the app?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Is there a specific way that the app should handle users who are using different types of browsers, such as Chrome, Firefox, Safari, or Edge?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I consider adding any kind of gamification elements to the app, such as badges or achievements?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Is there a specific way that the app should handle users who are using different types of operating systems, such as Windows, macOS, Linux, iOS, or Android?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I consider adding any kind of integration with hardware devices, such as MIDI controllers or other musical instruments?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Is there a specific way that the app should handle users who are using different types of input devices, such as mice, trackpads, or gamepads?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I consider adding any kind of integration with other web applications or services?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Is there a specific way that the app should handle users who are using different types of displays, such as retina displays or high-DPI screens?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I consider adding any kind of integration with accessibility tools or services?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Is there a specific way that the app should handle users who are using different types of browsers, such as mobile browsers or desktop browsers?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Should I consider adding any kind of integration with analytics or tracking services?</question>
    <question answer="NO">Is there a specific way that the app should handle users who are using different types of networks, such as Wi-Fi, cellular data, or Ethernet?</question>
</questions>